该死
Damn it.
快
Come on.
就是这个了
This is the one!
中头奖了
Jackpot!
都在这儿了
It's all here.
这究竟是什么意思
Meaning what, exactly?
意思是田鼠
Meaning, uh, you know, field mice
你有了筑巢的松鼠
and, you know, you got your nest-building squirrel.
你有了...  管它呢
You got your... Whatever.
为美德喝彩三声
Three cheers for morality.
-那东西呢  -什么东西
- Hey, where's the, uh -- - What?
那个...
You know, the...
好好说话
Use your words.
你碎了你桌下的文件吗
Did you shred the files under your desk?
碎了
Yes.
行
Okay.
你的名片盒呢
What about your Rolodex?
碎了  还有文件柜里的东西
Yes, and everything in the filing cabinets
-还有保险柜里的  -厕所里的
- and the safe and -- - The stuff in the bathroom.
原创翻译  双语字幕
你不是搞定了吗
You did that yourself, remember?
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
是的  是的
Right, right.
翻译     肉松   吃冰棒
翻译     窝车   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译     joy_bwl
校对     喃喃
时间轴     念念   今   大葱
后期     8T
总监     喃喃
行了  搞定了
All right, that's it.
-我走了  -帮我个忙
- I'm going. - Do me a favor.
你带上那些东西
Take those with you.
扔到至少八公里外的地方
Drop them off at least five miles from here
扔进不同的垃圾桶
-- in separate Dumpsters.
没错
Oh, right. Um...
好吧
Fine.
如果警察找你问话
Okay, when the cops come talk to you --
他们一定会的  你会怎么跟他们说
and they will -- what are you gonna tell them?
"找我律师"
"Talk to my attorney."
没错
Yeah.
跟他们说  吉米派你来的  行吗
Tell 'em, uh, Jimmy sent ya. Okay?
十一月十二日下午三点你会在哪儿
And where are you gonna be November 12th at 3:00 P.M.?
我会在那儿  但如果三点整没响铃  我就走
I'll be there, but if it doesn't ring at 3:00 on the dot, I'm gone.
别担心  会响铃的
Don't worry. It's gonna ring.
好吧  那
Well, I guess, uh...
就这样
that's it.
这一路不容易啊
Quite a ride, huh?
得了吧
Yep.
我需要一个新滤尘器
I need a new dust filter
胡夫超强力吸尘器升级版  60型号的
for my Hoover Max Extract Pressure Pro, model 60.
可以帮我准备吗
Can you help me with that?
自取
Pickup.
有多急  很着急
How hot? Red hot.
我知道在哪儿
I know where that is.
我会去的
I'll be there.
绝命律师
第四季 第五集
CC通讯
有人在监听吗
本店出售隐私
没错
Yep.
最高级别的隐私
Maximum privacy.
市面上最好的
It's the best money can buy.
十个  不  不行
10? No. Can't do it.
大家都想要
Everyone wants these things.
六个  好  六个可以
6? Um, yeah. Yeah, I can do 6.
行  待会儿见
Okay. See you later.
欢迎光临CC通讯
Welcome to CC Mobile.
抱歉让您久等了
Sorry to ‭keep you waiting.
有什么可以帮您
What can I do for you?
这里卖隐私吗
So, privacy sold here?
没错  正是这里
Yep. This is the place.
不被谁发现的隐私
Privacy from who?
明知故问  你懂的
Come on. You know.
比如政府
Like, the government?
可能是
Could be.
比如国税局
Like the IRS?
没错
Bingo!
那
So...
如果你有现金交易的生意
So, uh, say you got a cash-based business.
比如承包业务吗
Like a contracting business?
承包  可以  可以
Contracting. Could be. Could be.
你也许不会每分钱都上报
Maybe you don't report every single penny.
谁会呢  对吧
I mean, who does, right?
你怎么做生意
How are you doing that business?
电话
On the phone.
你怎么安排会面
How are you scheduling appointments?
电话
On the phone.
你怎么安排收付款  电话
How are you arranging payments? On the phone.
谁在监听呢  没错
And who's listening? That's right.
他们一清二楚
They know every lick and tittle.
你这时候偷税漏税
So, you're living your life free and easy
但有一天  他们会择时
and then one day, at a time of their choosing --
突击你  好好对付你
bam! -- they bring the hammer down to Chinatown.
-天啊  -惊讶就对了
- Jesus. - Jesus is right.
我告诉你  这些人不是闹着玩的
I'm telling you, these guys don't fool around.
他们会把你查得"皮肉不存"
And they will clean your bones
比食人鱼群还快
faster than a school of piranhas.
我告诉你我的工作
I'll tell you what I do.
我提供的东西叫做"信息卫生"
I practice something we call information hygiene.
无影无踪
Can't be traced.
无迹可寻
Can't be tracked.
可以让你一干二净
That'll keep you clean as a whistle.
他们不知道  就没法对付你
What they don't know can't hurt you
只要你定期用这个东西
especially if you use it only once per.
这很关键
You know, that's kind of key.
定期
"Once per"?
定期是多久
Once per what?
每周  每天  每次通话
Once per week, once per day, once per call.
依情况而定
I mean, depends on the nature of your situation.
多少钱
How much are they?
保证比被审计花钱少
They're cheaper than an audit, guaranteed.
可惜
Unfortunately...
怎么
What?
这台已经被预订了
Well, this one's spoken for.
我的货很紧俏
My supply is very short.
人们都抢疯了
Well, people are gobbling these up like Tic Tacs.
已预订
勿售
再次感谢
Thanks again.
告诉你朋友哦
Tell your friends.
丹佛国际机场
喂
Hello?
欢迎来到美国
Welcome to the USA.
用杯架里的预付停车票
Use the prepaid parking ticket
离开停车场
in the cup holder to exit the lot.
右转
Make a right.
沿70号州际公路往西
Follow the signs for I-70 west.
-收到了吗  -70号州际公路往西  收到
- Got it? - 70 headed west. Yes.
手机留在身边
Keep the phone close by
我大概二十分钟后再给你打电话
and I'll call you in about 20 minutes
告诉你接下来怎么做  明白吗
and talk you through the rest of it, okay?
我明白  好的
I understand. Yes.
我到了  路标上写着238
‭Yes. I'm here, mark 238
但这儿没人
but there's nobody here.
你需要上厕所吗
You need to relieve yourself?
不用
No.
-你在哪  -真不用吗
- Where are you? - You sure?
要是需要的话  还是现在就上一趟吧
Because if you do, I suggest you do it now.
之后要很久才能上厕所了
You're not going to have another chance for awhile.
我真不用
As I said, I'm fine.
随便你
Suit yourself.
打开后备箱  你会看到一个面罩
Pop the trunk. Inside, you'll see a hood.
拿出来  关上后备箱
Take it out. Close the trunk.
把行李放在身边
Place your luggage next to you
戴上面罩
and put the hood on.
明白吗
That clear?
你要我戴着面罩站在这儿
You want me to stand here with a hood on my head?
这是规矩
Those are the rules.
往前走
Step forward.
前面路很颠簸
We're gonna hit some rough road.
伸手  你左边有条带子
There's a strap for you to hold on to
可以抓着它
if you reach out to your left.
喝水吗
You want some water?
不了谢谢
No, thanks.
下来  往前走
Step down. Then walk.
有台阶
There are stairs.
上来
Step up.
往前走
Forward.
很好
That's good.
到了
Right there.
到底是哪儿
So, where, exactly?
入口得在那后面
The entrance will be back there.
你必须待在这栋建筑之内
You need to stay within the footprint of the building.
好了
All right.
能做吗
You can do it?
没问题
Absolutely.
要多久
How long will it take?
我想说七个月
I want to say seven months
但六个月我应该能完成
but I think I could do it in six.
哪怕要爆破
Even with blasting?
地质学家的报告写得很详尽
The geologist's report was very thorough
如果有正确的设备  先进的方法
and with the right equipment, modern methods
其实无需爆破
blasting will be quite unnecessary...
如果你老板付的酬劳令我满意的话
assuming your employer is willing to meet my price.
钱不是问题
Price isn't an issue.
收到
Copy That.
不爆破  挖十七米
So, 56 feet down with no blasting
只在夜里工作  最多七个月完工
working nights only, ‭you're saying seven months, max?
我们以前挖过一条
My men and I dug a tunnel
穿越边境到埃尔帕索市中心的地道
under the border into downtown El Paso
长七百五十米  没被发现
3/4 of a kilometer long, undetected.
只用了十七周
That took us 17 weeks.
那次都成功了  这次当然也没问题
If I can do that, I can certainly do this.
喂
Yeah?
对
Yep.
我也是这么想的
That's what I thought.
谢谢你跑一趟
Thank you for your time.
什么
Pardon?
欢迎登机
拉住短的那头
Pull the short end.
-太紧了  -习惯就好了
- It's too tight. - Live with it.
法官跟你说话的时候你应该看哪儿
Where do you look when the judge is talking to you?
看他的眼睛
In the eyes.
应该怎么称呼法官
And what do you call the judge?
-"先生"吗  -"女士"
- "Sir"? - "Ma'am."
更妥当的称呼是"法官阁下"
Or, better still, "Your Honor."
坐那儿  别碰领带
Sit over there. And leave that alone.
无罪  你开玩笑吧
Not guilty? You can't be serious.
这种案子还用庭审吗
On what planet would you take this to trial?
这个案子你应该配合我
You should work with me on this one.
这孩子扔煤渣砖砸碎了珠宝店的窗户
The kid threw a cinder block through a jewelry-store window
而且我有目击证人
and I have a witness.
讲真  我够宽宏的了
Frankly, ‭I'm being generous.
我想要六个月缓刑  减去已服刑期  不坐牢
I want six months probation, time served, no jail.
我还想中彩票  养几条拉布拉多呢
And I want to win the lottery and breed labradoodles.
行啊  比尔
Nice try, Bill.
你逃不掉的
You're not gonna get away with it.
逃不掉什么
Away with what?
拜托
Come on.
你不是装傻吧
You're not gonna play dumb, are you?
请你开导我
Please enlighten me.
逮捕他的警官还没有告知他有沉默权
The arresting officers took the first part of my guy's statement
就录了一部分口供
before he was Mirandized.
他们收集的证据都是基于那次审问
They collected evidence based on that interview
而且你一清二楚
and you knew all about it.
那跟这无关
That's irrelevant.
你怎么...你为什么能...
How would you -- Why would you even...
你的委托人犯事了
Your guy did it.
比尔  你不想让我跟法官提这件事吧
Bill, you don't want me ‭to bring this up with the judge.
不仅这个案子你会败诉
Not only will your case be DOA
她还会在你记录里添上一笔
but she will rip you a new one on the record.
-法官才不信你说的呢  -她会的
- The judge is not buying any of that. - I think she will.
证据都在这里
It's all right here.
听着  我
Listen, I --
好吧  十个月监禁
Okay. 10 months jail.
六个月缓刑  减去已服刑期
6 months probation, time served.
这孩子需要个回头的机会
This kid needs a chance to turn his life around
而不是烂在狱中  加入黑帮
not rot in prison and join a gang.
你开玩笑吗
Are you joking?
我们刚开始可是十八个月监禁
We started at 18 months jail.
随便你
Up to you.
八个月监禁
Eight months jail.
四个月缓刑
Four months probation.
-等等  不是六个月吗  -你让我心烦
- Wait. What happened to six? - You're annoying me.
你别跟我玩博弈
You can't play chicken with me.
你可玩不过我
I invented chicken.
好吧
Okay.
行吧
Fine.
六个月监禁  一年缓刑
Six months jail time, one year probation.
四个月我做不到
I can't make four months fly.
不可能  绝对不可能
It's impossible, completely impossible.
你没时间跟我耗
You don't have time for this.
比尔  我就剩一个委托人了
Bill, I only have one other client
还是家银行
and it's a bank.
我有的是时间
I have all the time in the world.
全体起立  有请尊敬的利佩兹法官
All rise for the Honorable Judge Lipitz.
-法官来了  -对
- The judge. - Yeah.
-CR2003114721  -行吧  四个月
- CR2003114721... - Fine. Four months.
-四个月缓刑吗  -大卫·埃斯特拉达公诉案
- Four months probation? - State versus David Estrada.
-对  -早上好
- Yes. ‭- Good morning.
请坐
Please be seated.
法官阁下  请问我可以开始吗
If I may, Your Honor.
请讲  韦克斯勒女士
Yes, Ms. Wexler.
我很高兴地说  原被告双方
I'm happy to say the defense and prosecution
达成了一致
have reached an agreement.
等等  站着别动
Hey, wait. No. Stand still.
领带是我的  记得吗
This is mine, remember?
我不想催你
I don't mean to rush you
但是会面十五分钟后开始  还要赶路
but the meeting's in 15, and with traffic...
好  知道了  谢谢
Okay. Got it. Thanks.
会有个假释官跟在我屁股后面
I'm gonna have a probation officer on my ass
足足四个月吗
for fourth months?
大卫  听我说
David, listen to me.
下面你要这么做
Here's what you're gonna do.
今天  在你离开这里之后
Today, after you leave here
你直接去你祖父的饭店
you will go straight to your grandfather's restaurant
去求他给你个工作  什么活儿都行
and you will beg him for a job, any job.
他让你去刷烤架你就刷烤架
If he tells you to scrub the grill, you scrub the grill.
他让你去扫厕所
If he tells you to clean the toilet
你就去扫厕所
you clean the toilet.
你得准时上班
You will show up on time.
面带微笑
You will smile.
把"请"和"谢谢"挂在嘴边
You will say "Please" and "Thank you."
你得夹起尾巴做人
You will keep your nose clean.
明白了吗
You understand?
如果你不这么做  你就得进监狱
Because if you don't, you will go to jail.
关着成年罪犯的真正的监狱
Grown-up jail with grown-up bad guys.
想想后果吧  大卫
Picture that, David.
你好好地想想
Really picture it.
还有  记住了
And know this --
再有下回我可就不管你了
I'm not gonna do a damn thing about it next time.
明白了吗
You got it?
很好
Okay.
不  不行
Nope. No.
本地新闻  付费节目
同位素队对阵雨人队
阿尔伯克基市政会议
阿尔伯克基家居园艺
高尔夫大师赛
足球天地:皇家马德里对阵巴塞罗那
日瓦格医生(1965年)
黄金女郎
公众自制节目
社区电视节目
不行  不
Uh...no. Nope.
等等  你瞧
Wait. Wait. Hey, look.
《日瓦格医生》快开始放了
"Doctor Zhivago" is about to start.
冰天雪地里的一群美男子
Lots of attractive men in the snow.
这是你最爱的类型
That's your favorite genre.
抱歉  我不能陪你看
I'm sorry. I can't.
我还有好多梅萨维德银行的事要做
I have tons of Mesa Verde to catch up on.
你不是雇了个助理律师吗
Isn't that why you have a paralegal?
但我得审核她的工作呀
Well, I have to review her work.
你看吧
You watch.
多谢
Thanks.
开着电视你能工作吗
Can you work with the TV on?
我的注意力非同寻常
I have tremendous powers of concentration.
你看吧  没事的
Go ahead. It's fine.
不会打扰到我的
It wasn't bothering me.
是啊  我知道  我只是
Yeah, I know. I just, uh
想起来我还有点工作上的事要处理
realized there's something I need to to do at work.
现在可是晚上九点
At 9 o'clock at night?
是啊  这是我第一周上班  知道吗
Yeah, well, it's my first week, you know?
我想留下个好印象
I want to make a good impression.
我才刚刚上手  所以...
I'm just getting the hang of the system, so...
好的  那我就去卧室吧
Okay. I'll just go in the bedroom.
大可不必  你有工作
Absolutely not. You have work.
我也有工作  没事的
I have work. It's okay.
好的
‭Okay.
没什么的  你不用等我了
It's all good. Don't wait up.
洗衣店
嘿  你们好
Hey! ‭How's it going?
手机了解一下
How you guys set for phones?
我们有手机了
We got phones.
私人手机
Private phones.
滚蛋吧  条子
Beat it, narc.
得了吧
Oh, come on.
条子会开这种烂车吗
Would a narc drive this piece of shit?
把它拿回去扣押着吧  条子
Take it back to impound, narc.
蠢货
Loser.
*我在街头混日子*
*I play the street life*
*因为我无家可归*
*Because there's no place I can go*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*我不知人生有其他活法*
*It's the only life I know*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*我有万千面孔随时变幻*
*And there's a thousand parts to play*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*直到一朝失手把命丢*
*Until you play your life away*
*在人前你光鲜亮丽*
*You let the people see just who you wanna be*
*每晚都闪耀如巨星*
*And every night, you shine just like a superstar*
狗狗屋
*这就是我的处世之道*
*That's how the life is played*
*兜里空空却强装大佬*
*A 10-cent masquerade*
*衣着光鲜  四处风流*
*You dress, you walk, you talk*
*你想变成谁就是谁*
*You're who you think you are*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*你能青春常在*
*You can run away from time*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*只用花一分一毫*
*For a nickel or a dime*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*但你最好不要变老*
*But you better not get old*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
*否则你将穷困潦倒*
*Or you're gonna feel the cold*
*街头人生*
*Street life*
回见
Later.
好的
Yeah
是啊  肥仔就不该这么骑车
Yeah, no fat boy's supposed to ride like that.
你们好
Hi. How are you?
这车可真不赖
That's a beautiful ride.
你们好啊
Hey. How's it going?
你那个纹身
Did you get, uh --
你那个纹身是在洛斯卢娜斯弄的吗
Did you get that ink in Los Lunas?
是在拉斯克鲁斯
Las Cruces.
差不多嘛
Off by one.
你也进去过
And you've been inside?
不  还没这个荣幸
No, I haven't had the honor
但我以前是名律师
but I used to be a lawyer.
重点是"以前"
Emphasis on "Used to be."
我帮过许多像你这样
And I helped a lot of gentlemen such as yourself --
以及你朋友这样的先生们
and your friends here.
我在帮助新墨西哥惩戒机构里的委托人时
And one thing I learned from working with my clients
学到的一个经验就是
in the New Mexico corrections system
私密谈话要少  频率要低
is that private conversations are few and far between.
永远有人窃听电话线
The man is always listening on those land lines.
您是明白人不用我多说
So word to the wise --
你要想和号子里的朋友谈话
if you want to talk to your friends on the inside
有个简单的方法
there is a simple solution.
是吗  什么方法
Yeah? What's that?
这个小宝贝
This little baby.
是市面上最小的型号
it's the most compact model on the market.
可以藏匿在任何地方
It could be hidden in any number of places.
如果你用现金从我这里买
And if you buy it from me with cash
绝对没法追踪来源
it's completely untraceable.
多少钱
How much?
一路顺风
Keep the rubber side down!
对不住  你们没机会了
Sorry, guys. You had your chance.
我全卖光了
I'm all sold out.
把你的钱给我
Give me your money.
我是个条子  记得吗
I'm a narc, remember?
不  我们看见你的现金了
No. We saw you got cash.
-交出来  -想得美
- Hand it over. - Nice try.
听着  阿呆  阿傻  阿瓜
Look, Pee Wee, Scooter, Skippy
见到你们很高兴
it was very good to meet you boys.
祝你们的青少年成就计划顺利
Good luck with the junior achievement project.
我要走了
I-I got to go.
拿钱
Aah! ‭Get it.
跑  跑  跑
Go. Go. Go.
快跑
Come on, man.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不是故意吵醒你的
I didn't mean to wake you.
没事
It's okay.
发生什么事了
What happened?
我被打劫了
I got mugged.
天呐  真冰
Jesus, that's cold.
所以呢  敷着别动
So? Keep it on there.
你确定不去急救室吗
Are you sure you don't want to go to the E.R. just to be safe?
不了  我没事  真的
No, I'm fine, really.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在检查你的瞳孔大小是否一致
I'm checking that your pupils are the same size.
我没事  我发誓
I'm okay. I swear.
对不起
‭Sorry.
瞧瞧我们
Look at us.
我们就像马修·布雷迪[战地记者]镜头下的人
We're like a Mathew Brady photo.
是啊  我觉得还得有架大炮才像
Yeah. I think you'd need a cannon to really sell that.
是在狗狗屋那发生的吗
So, this happened at The Dog House?
是的
Yeah.
凌晨一点半的时候
1:30 in the morning?
我记不清时间了
I lost track of time.
我车停得太远了
And, uh, parked too far away, so...
我太蠢了
It was just dumb.
你报警了吗
Did you call the police?
没有  还有什么意义呢
Nah. ‭What's the point?
我也不想后半夜进城去
Anyway, I don't feel like spending the rest of the night downtown
盯着那几个屁孩儿的大头照看
looking at mug shots of kids with stringy hair.
我到底是怎么了
What the hell's the matter with me?
听起来你是在错误的时间
It sounds like you were just
出现在了错误的地点
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
回想当年  我一英里外就能
Back in the day, I would have spotted
嗅出这些小瘪三
those low-rent little skeeves from a mile away
他们也知道不要来惹我
and they would have known not to roll me.
真的吗  怎么知道的
Yeah? How would they have known that?
说不好  就是...
I don't. Just...
因为那时候
Well, because back then, uh...
我就是他们中的一员
I guess I was one of them.
那些日子已经过去了
Well, those days are over.
是啊
Yeah.
但是...
But, uh...
什么
What?
知道吗
You know what?
我觉得明天
I think tomorrow
我可能会打给那个心理医生
I might, uh, call that shrink.
试试也无妨  对吗
Couldn't hurt, right?
对  无妨
No. Couldn't hurt.
德妮丝
Denise!
我是金·韦克斯勒
It's Kim Wexler!
德妮丝  你怎么还在这
Denise, why are you still here?
你应该一小时前在法庭和我碰面的
You were supposed to meet me in court an hour ago.
所以我错过了  对吗
So, I missed it, right?
还没
Not yet.
我让书记推迟了你的听证会
I got the clerk to push your hearing
但我们现在得走了
but we've got to go now.
我不能去
I can't.
我吓坏了
I'm freaking out.
抱歉  韦克斯勒女士  我不能坐牢
I'm sorry, Ms. Wexler, but I can't go to jail.
我不能保证你不用坐牢
I can't promise you no jail time.
但我肯定的是
But what I do know for sure
如果你现在不和我一起去法庭
is that if you don't ‭come with me right now to court
法官会给你开一张法庭拘票
the judge is gonna issue a bench warrant
到那时就肯定要坐牢了
and then jail is a done deal.
德妮丝  你可以做到的
Denise, you can do this.
你是初犯
It's your first offense.
剂量小于两盎司
It was ‭under two ounces.
相信我  我很在行
Trust me. I'm good at this.
要不你去换件好点的衣服
Why don't you change into something nice.
我们一起面对
We'll do this together.
你好  佩奇
Hi, Paige.
金  我们有大麻烦了
Kim, we've got a huge problem.
送去丹佛和弗莱哥斯达的分行文件中
There's a major error in the branch paperwork
有一个重大错误
that went out to Denver and Flagstaff.
需要马上解决
It has to be fixed ASAP.
很不幸  我现在有事要处理
Unfortunately, I'm right in the middle of something
但我四点可以到
but I can be there at 4:00.
-现在就过来  -抱歉  我没空
- I need you now. - Oh, I'm sorry. I can't.
我不知道该怎么说  佩奇
I don't know what to tell you, Paige.
我只是  现在过不来
I just -- not right now.
-但是  金  这是...  -抱歉
- But, Kim, this is -- I'm sorry.
德妮丝  到时间了
Denise, it's time!
快点  我们得走了
Come on! We got to go!
你看起来很不错
You look great.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了  好好加油
All right. Let's go get 'em.
佩奇  我很抱歉
Paige, I'm so sorry.
-我们现在来解决吧  -已经解决了
- Let's get this fixed right now. - It's fixed.
我不得不发动所有员工
I had to pull everyone on the floor
重新打印并校对这份文件
to re-type and proof the submission
因为文件不在我们手上
because we didn't have the files
而你的助理律师不知道文件在哪
and your paralegal didn't know where they were.
我真的很想亲自向凯文道歉
I'd really like to apologize to Kevin personally, as well
如果他有空的话
if he's available.
他没空
He's not.
让我把话说清楚
Let me be very clear.
问题不在于出了这个差错
The mistake is not the issue here.
所有人都会犯错
Everyone makes mistakes.
但我需要知道你是全情投入的
But I need to know your head is in this.
你向我们保证
You made us a promise
你会把精力全都放在梅萨维德上
that Mesa Verde would be your sole focus.
需要你的时候  你就得出现
When we need you, we need you.
我们不是你可以挂断电话的委托人
We're not a client you hang up on.
真的很抱歉  佩奇
I'm really sorry, Paige.
再也不会发生这样的事了
It'll never happen again.
希望如此
I hope not.
我好难受  我要吐车里了
Mir ist so schlecht. Ich kotz gleich ins Auto.
请说英文
Speak English, please.
我要吐了
I'm going to throw up.
建议你不要
I suggest you don't.
忍住  我们就快到了
Now, hold on. We're almost there.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你没事吧
You okay?
好点了
Better.
不好意思
Pardon.
我吃了晕车药  但不管用
I take the Dramamine, but it doesn't help.
好吧
Okay.
那边吗
Over there?
那边
Over there.
怎么样
So?
我可以开始挖前
Before I can begin excavation
一定得要给现有的结构做支撑
I must support the existing structure
来避免塌方
to avoid a cave-in.
通常  这项工作需要打桩机
Normally, this would involve the piling rig
从地上进行
working from above.
但又不能在地上引人注目  对吧
But there can be no activity visible from the surface, hmm?
所以我必须用连续旋翼式螺钻建咬合桩
So I must construct secant walls of CFA piles
完全在地下工作
working completely underground.
难度很大
Um, difficult.
下一步  我得想办法将工字梁
Next, I must somehow place I-beams
穿过咬合桩围护墙顶部安装好
across the top of the secant walls
来支撑地板和机器
to support the floor and the machinery.
抱歉
Excuse me.
这样才能开始挖掘
Only now can I fully excavate.
我需要移走大约一千七百立方米的泥土
I will need to move perhaps 1,700 cubic meters of dirt.
这意味着要用卡车运输大约两百趟
That means trucking out about 200 loads.
挖到这种深度  肯定会碰到岩石
Going this deep, we will surely hit rock
那么就要进行爆破工作
which means blasting.
我需要这块区域的公用设施施工图
I will need schematics of utility in the area.
可以
You'll get those.
一旦这里被清理干净  我就开始防水处理
Once the space is fully cleared, I can waterproof
然后为挡土墙制造铸件
then fabricate casts for the retaining walls
浇筑混凝土
and pour concrete.
我们需要...
We would need, uh...
大概一百五十立方米
About 150 cubic meters.
这只是个开始
This is just the beginning.
而这一切还必须要秘密进行
And all this in complete secrecy.
从我听到的声音来判断
Judging from the sounds I heard
我猜我们应该离城镇不远
I assume we are not far from a town.
环境方面也不太...理想
This is also not... optimal.
像这样的工程  很多很多事都有可能出错
A project like this, many, many things can go wrong.
所以  这是不可能的了
So, it's impossible?
危险  难度大
Dangerous, difficult
而且造价非常非常昂贵
and very, very expensive...
但并非不可能
not quite impossible.
古斯塔沃·弗林
Gustavo Fring.
很高兴认识你
A pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
维纳·齐格勒
Werner Ziegler.
可以了
You're good.
回见  马蒂
See you, Marty.
回见  吉米
See you, Jimmy.
-可以了吗  -好了  下一个
- Ready for me? - Okay, next.
霍华德
‭Howard.
你还好吧
Everything okay?
挺好的
Everything's fine.
你呢
And how are you doing?
就这样吧
I've been better.
我去地检办公室做诉前转移签到
I'm heading up to the D.A.'s office for my PPD check-in
所以...
so, you know...
哦
Yeah.
就那样
Anyway...
你真的没事吗
You sure you're okay?
我二十五分钟后
I'm supposed to be in court in, uh...
要上庭
about 25 minutes.
大案子
Big case?
不是
Not particularly.
所以发生什么事了
So, what's up?
没什么
Nothing.
只是...
Just...
你得过失眠症吗
You ever have insomnia?
没有
Not really.
太痛苦了  就算是死对头我也不咒他失眠
Wouldn't wish it on my worst enemy.
没有什么药能治吗
Don't they have pills for that?
抱歉
I'm -- I'm sorry.
我必须得问一下
I got to ask.
你到底怎么了
What's -- what's eating you?
吉米
Jimmy...
我已经告诉你够多的了
I think I've shared enough...
实际上是太多了
more than enough.
我们就说到这吧
Let's leave it at that.
明白了
I get it.
你知道吗  霍华德
You know what, Howard?
对自己好一点  去找医生看看
you do yourself a favor, and you go see someone.
我这里正好有一个心理医生的电话
I actually have the number of a shrink.
帮一个委托人找的
I got it for a client.
这个医生应该还不错
And he's supposed to be great.
我这里正好有
I think, um, I got it right here, actually.
谢谢
Uh, thanks.
我已经在看医生了
I'm already seeing someone.
真的吗
Really?
一周两次
Twice a week.
好医生吗
Is he any good?
是的
Yes.
见到你很高兴  霍华德
Good seeing you, Howard.
我也是
You too.
请稍等
Can you hold, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
是的  先生  我是史提夫·卡尔顿
Uh, yes, sir, this is, uh, Steve Carlton...
那么  我们刚才说到哪了
So, where were we?
社区服务
Community service.
社区服务  没错
Community service. Right.
看起来你的小时数已经完成了
Well, it looks like you completed your hours.
是的
Yep.
你的诉前转移费也交了
Your PPD fees are up to date.
你最近在哪里获得了合法雇佣来着...
And you've recently procured lawful employment at...
CC通讯
CC Mobile.
地址
Address?
路易斯安那大道8351号
8351 Louisiana Boulevard.
8351 Louisiana.
一周工作多少小时
How many hours a week?
这周是三十一个小时  以后我会工作更长时间
This week, uh, 31, but I'll pick up more.
下个月把工资条带来
Next month, bring pay stubs.
好的
Will do.
你是否和任何已知的罪犯有联系
Are you associating with any known criminals?
没有
No.
好的
All right.
第二个月看起来不错
Month two looks good.
你有没有想过诉前转移期结束后
Have you thought about what you're gonna do
要干点什么
once your PPD is up?
我有一些计划
I have some plans.
好的
Okay.
比如说...
Such as...
在那之前  我绝对会在每个月的
Until then, I'll show up here every second Monday of
第二个星期一出现在这里
the month like clockwork.
我要保住我在手机店的工作
I'm gonna keep my job at the cellphone store
在九个月二十四天后
and in 9 months and 24 days
拿回我的律师执照
I will get my law license back.
我和我的搭档会找一个新的办公室
My partner and I will get a new office.
跟以前的一样  但更大更好
It'll be like it was, but bigger and better.
一切都会好起来
Everything will be better.
我会有更多委托人
I'm gonna have more clients.
打赢更多的官司
I'm gonna win more cases.
我会成为一个好律师
I'm gonna be a damn good lawyer
-所有人都会知道  -好的
- and people are gonna know about it. - Okay.
所以...律师咯
So...lawyer.
对
Yeah.
律师
Lawyer.